http://www.airteamimages.com/cookies-privacy.php

Cookies and Privacy
What are cookies?
Cookies are small files which are stored in your web browser and are widely used in order to make websites work efficiently. This site uses cookies. Some of the cookies we use are essential for parts of this website function correctly - for example keeping track of items that you add to your shopping basket or remembering when you've logged into our customer area. Other cookies are less essential functionally but may be used to personalise your experience or track your journey through our site so that we can analyse the success of promotions. Other cookies may be from third parties such as social networking sites or affiliates.
Confidentiality Of Personal Information
AirTeamImages will not sell or give
your personal information to third parties.
Your personal information will be
kept confidential and will only be viewed by those AirTeamImages employees who
are authorised to view such information as part of their jobs.
However,
AirTeamImages may disclose personal information to law enforcement authorities
to enforce AirTeamImages’ rights against unauthorised access or attempted
unauthorised access to AirTeamImages information technology assets or in
response to law enforcement efforts.
AirTeamImages will also report to
appropriate law enforcement agencies any activities that are or may be unlawful
as well as e-mail containing, or implying, threats or other illegal activity.
Why are you telling me this?
Website operators (like us) are already required to give users information about the cookies they use and why they use them. Now - by European law - they also have to have your consent to store them in your browser and allow you to adjust your cookie settings at any time. You can make these adjustments on this page. To make things easy for you we've grouped our cookies into the most common sets with descriptions of what each cookie or set actually do. You can switch these sets on or off. Your new settings will take effect when you click the 'Save settings' button at the bottom of the page.
Important to note - if you decide not to have certain cookies stored in your browser you'll lose the functionality that they allow, so please read the description of the cookie or set of cookies carefully.
If you'd like continue shopping as normal and consent to accept all cookies for this site - simply click the button below, we'll return you to the homepage and stop reminding you to check your settings.
Copyright AirTeamImages 2003-2020
Images © the respective photographers
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Purchase & Returns Policy
TravelTeamImages
SeaTeamImages
This site uses Cookies. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit some websites. We use cookies to maximise your experience and make our website easier for you to use. Learn more
close
Follow @airteamimages
AirTeamImages.com is the world's largest and most respected aviation stock image library on the web with large collections of airplane pictures and aircraft photos
Updated: 30/08/2019
